popbitch.com 2015-06-24

# Popbitch Magazine Privacy Policy

### [Popbitch Magazine Privacy Policy](http://popbitch.com/home/privacy-policy/ "Permanent link to Popbitch Magazine Privacy Policy")

**1\. General**  
This policy covers the Popbitch Magazine app for iOS and Android platforms, produced by Popbitch. If you have any questions about your personal information beyond what is addressed here, please email [support@popbitch.com](mailto:support@popbitch.com)  

**2\. Information Collected**  
There are two types of information you will be asked to input: _Identifiable information_ and _Non-Identifiable information_.

**2.1** _Identifiable information_ will be used by Apple, Amazon or Google Market in order to verify and maintain your subscription. This information will be used for no other purpose by Popbitch. Occasionally we (Popbitch) may ask you for identifying information, in the form of reader surveys, competitions, subscription offers or others. In that case, we will only use your information for the purpose for which it was provided. Should you wish us to not use your information after you have supplied it, please inform us at any time – [support@popbitch.com](mailto:support@popbitch.com)

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product.

Popbitch will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties, with the exception of trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, and we insist that these parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

**2.2** _Non-identifiable information_ will occasionally be gathered in the form of user analytics. This statistical informational will be used for editorial and internal purposes, in order to improve the magazine and the service for our readers. The information will be given to us in aggregate form and will, in no way, be attached to any identifying information such as name, username, address or online ID. The service we use to perform this is Google Analytics.

This non-personally identifiable, aggregated visitor information may be used in our promotional and professional materials for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**3\. Links**  
There are links within each issue of Popbitch Magazine, which will take you to third party websites – the content and practices over which Popbitch has no control. Popbitch accepts no responsibility or liability for any of the activities of these sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our app and welcome any feedback about these sites.

  **4\. Cookies**  
We use cookies on our website. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow it). It enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to help us understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. You can visit our site anonymously.

  **5\. Payment Information**  
We use third parties to collect your subscription payments. As such Popbitch is never given your personal payment information. If you wish to know what happens with your credit or debit card details (or other payment method) you should refer to the Apple Store, Google Market or Amazon Appstore policies (depending on which device/marketplace you use)

  **6\. Other**  
By using the Popbitch magazine app, you consent to our privacy policy. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

  If you have any further questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

  **7\. Contact Details**  
Email: [support@popbitch.com](mailto:support@popbitch.com)

  Popbitch  
61 Poland Street  
London  
W1D 7NU
